{
    "subject": "Anne_Jeffreys",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Robert_Sterling",
    "human_readable": "Anne Jeffreys is married to Robert Sterling.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9881933331489563,
            "question": "Is Robert Sterling married to Anne Jeffreys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8916566967964172,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Anne Jeffreys and Robert Sterling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8663313984870911,
            "question": "Who is Anne Jeffreys married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8510885834693909,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Anne Jeffreys and Robert Sterling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8281974792480469,
            "question": "Who are Anne Jeffreys and Robert Sterling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6987454295158386,
            "question": "To whom is Anne Jeffreys legally bound in marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5864224433898926,
            "question": "What is the name of Anne Jeffreys' spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5781313180923462,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Anne Jeffreys' husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5142542123794556,
            "question": "Who shares a marital relationship with Anne Jeffreys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5113359689712524,
            "question": "What is the nature of the bond between Anne Jeffreys and Robert Sterling?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Anne Jeffreys is married to Robert Sterling.",
            "html": "yago_24774_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital relationship with Anne Jeffreys?",
            "html": "yago_24774_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Anne Jeffreys' husband?",
            "html": "yago_24774_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Anne Jeffreys' spouse?",
            "html": "yago_24774_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24774_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24774_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24774_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24774_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24774_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24774_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24774_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24774_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24774_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24774_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Anne Jeffreys is married to Robert Sterling\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that Anne Jeffreys and Robert Sterling were married for 54 years (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_24774/re-ranker-msmarco/48.txt) and had three children together (Jeffrey, Dana, and Tyler). This information supports the triple that Anne Jeffreys is married to Robert Sterling."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Anne Jeffreys is married to Robert Sterling.\" The text states, \"Anne Jeffreys and Robert Sterling were married for 54 years before Robert Sterling died,\" indicating a marital relationship between Anne Jeffreys and Robert Sterling."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}